{
    "subject": "resource/California_State_University",
    "predicate": "property/type",
    "object": "resource/Public_university",
    "human_readable": "California State University is a public university.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.98821622133255,
            "question": "Is California State University a public university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.885578453540802,
            "question": "Is California State University a private institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8209282755851746,
            "question": "What type of institution is California State University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7643640637397766,
            "question": "Where is California State University located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6816814541816711,
            "question": "Can anyone attend California State University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6437608003616333,
            "question": "What are some of the majors offered at California State University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5487072467803955,
            "question": "Does California State University have graduate programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4987066090106964,
            "question": "Does California State University offer undergraduate programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4526764154434204,
            "question": "What are some of the research areas at California State University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3273294270038605,
            "question": "Are there tuition fees at California State University?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=California State University is a public university.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8656_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the research areas at California State University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8656_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does California State University offer undergraduate programs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8656_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does California State University have graduate programs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8656_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8656_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as all five documents mention that the California State University (CSU) is a four-year public university."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references supporting that the California State University (CSU) is a public university. For example, one document states, \"The California State University, also known as a CSU, is a public four-year college funded by the government.\" This supports the triple \"California State University is a public university.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}